Guide to the Othniel Charles Marsh Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- General correspondence, 1814-1903; Series I
  - Chandler, Alfred D., 1871-1872; cuid236 (Box 6, Folder 235)
  - Chandler, Charles F., 1882-1895; cuid237 (Box 6, Folder 236)
  - Chandler, George, 1892; cuid238 (Box 6, Folder 237)
  - Chandler, S. C., 1895; cuid239 (Box 6, Folder 238)
  - Chandler, T. P., Jr., 1871; cuid240 (Box 6, Folder 239)
  - Chandler, William E., 1883-1884; cuid241 (Box 6, Folder 240)
  - Chaplain, T. C., 1886-1889; cuid242 (Box 6, Folder 241)
  - Charnay, Desire, 1886; cuid243 (Box 6, Folder 242)
  - Cheney, H. G., 1873; cuid244 (Box 6, Folder 243)
  - Chester, Albert H., 1866-1867; cuid245 (Box 6, Folder 244)
  - Chester, Greville I., 1869; cuid246 (Box 6, Folder 245)
  - Chew, Annie, 1889; cuid247 (Box 6, Folder 246)
  - Chew, John W., 1872-1877; cuid248 (Box 6, Folder 247)
  - Chew, John W., 1882-1883; cuid249 (Box 6, Folder 248)
  - Childs, A.F., 1880-1882; cuid250 (Box 6, Folder 249)
  - Childs, C., 1868-1869; cuid251 (Box 6, Folder 250)
  - Chilton, R. H., 1869; cuid252 (Box 6, Folder 251)
  - Christian, Janes M., 1872; cuid253 (Box 6, Folder 253)
  - Clark, Elam, 1870; cuid254 (Box 7, Folder 254)
  - Clark, Fred A., 1876; cuid255 (Box 7, Folder 255)
  - Clark, John B., 1884; cuid256 (Box 7, Folder 256)
  - Clarke, Frank Wigglesworth (1847-1931), 1891-1893; cuid257 (Box 7, Folder 257)
  - Clarke, George A., 1885-1886; cuid258 (Box 7, Folder 258)
  - Clayton, T. C., 1891; cuid259 (Box 7, Folder 259)
  - Cleaves, Thomas P., 1885; cuid260 (Box 7, Folder 260)
  - Cleburne, William C., 1873-1881; cuid261 (Box 7, Folder 261)
  - Clifford, Hank C., 1873-1875; cuid262 (Box 7, Folder 262)
  - Clifford, Hank C., 1876-1892; cuid263 (Box 7, Folder 263)
  - Cody, William Frederick (1846-1917), 1873-1874; cuid264 (Box 7, Folder 264)
  - Coffin, Charles E., 1888; cuid265 (Box 7, Folder 265)
  - Coffin, John Huntington Crane, 1878-1887; cuid266 (Box 7, Folder 266)
  - Cohen, Joseph, 1887; cuid267 (Box 7, Folder 267)
  - Colbeau, Julie, undated; cuid268 (Box 7, Folder 268)
  - Colby, J.C., 1888; cuid269 (Box 7, Folder 269)
  - Collett, John (1828-1899), 1869-1877; cuid270 (Box 7, Folder 270)
  - Collier, Maurice Dwight (1846-1906), 1876; cuid271 (Box 7, Folder 271)
  - Collier, Peter (1835-1896), 1884-1890; cuid272 (Box 7, Folder 272)
  - Collins, J. B., 1887; cuid273 (Box 7, Folder 273)
  - Collins, W. H., 1883-1895; cuid274 (Box 7, Folder 274)
  - Comfort, A.I., 1868; cuid275 (Box 7, Folder 275)
  - Comfort, George Fisk (1833-1910), 1866-1881; cuid276 (Box 7, Folder 276)
  - Comstock, Apollos (1836-1889), 1868; cuid277 (Box 7, Folder 277)
  - Comstock, Cyrus Ballou (1831-1910), 1884-1894; cuid278 (Box 7, Folder 278)
  - Comstock, Theodore Bryant (1849-1915), 1899; cuid279 (Box 7, Folder 279)
  - Condon, Thomas (1822-1907), 1870-1890; cuid280 (Box 7, Folder 280)
  - Coues, Elliott, 1872-1884; cuid281 (Box 7, Folder 281)
  - Congdon, J.H., 1868-1869; cuid282 (Box 7, Folder 282)
  - Conrad, Timothy Abbot (1803-1877), 1869; cuid283 (Box 7, Folder 283)
  - Cook, A. E., 1877; cuid284 (Box 7, Folder 284)
  - Cook, George Hammell (1818-1889), 1869; cuid285 (Box 7, Folder 285)
  - Cooke, Josiah Parsons (1827-1844), 1891-1892; cuid286 (Box 7, Folder 286)
  - Coon, Charles E., 1884; cuid287 (Box 7, Folder 287)
  - Cooper, George P., 1876-1878; cuid288 (Box 7, Folder 288)
  - Cooper, J.G., 1877-1888; cuid289 (Box 7, Folder 289)
  - Cope, Edward Drinker (1840-1897), 1868-1877; cuid290 (Box 7, Folder 290)
  - Coplen, G.W., 1876-1880; cuid291 (Box 7, Folder 291)
  - Corey, O.W., 1876; cuid292 (Box 7, Folder 292)
  - Cortis, 1876; cuid293 (Box 7, Folder 293)
  - Couchi, Igino, 1899; cuid294 (Box 7, Folder 294)
  - Coues, Elliott, cuid295
    General note
    see Cones
  - Cowles, James Lewis (1843-1922), 1878; cuid296 (Box 7, Folder 295)
  - Cowles, Louise F., 1898; cuid297 (Box 7, Folder 296)
  - Cowles, S., 1868-1869; cuid298 (Box 7, Folder 297)
  - Cowsh, J.C., 1861; cuid299 (Box 7, Folder 298)
  - Cox, Edward Travers (1821-1907), 1871; cuid300 (Box 7, Folder 299)
  - Cox, Samuel Sullivan (1824-1889), 1884; cuid301 (Box 7, Folder 300)
  - Craft, Edwin, [1870?]; cuid302 (Box 7, Folder 301)
  - Cragin, Francis Whitternore (1858-?), 1894; cuid303 (Box 7, Folder 302)
  - Crane, E. H., 1894; cuid304 (Box 7, Folder 303)
  - Craven, Gus, 1889-1891; cuid305 (Box 7, Folder 304)
  - Crawford, Erasmus, 1879-1881; cuid306 (Box 7, Folder 305)
  - Credner, Dr. Hermann (1843-1933), 1896; cuid307 (Box 7, Folder 306)
  - Creevey, John K., 1890; cuid308 (Box 7, Folder 307)
  - Crisand, Emil, 1880-1898; cuid309 (Box 7, Folder 308)
  - Croffut, William Augustus (1835-1915), 1890; cuid310 (Box 7, Folder 309)
  - Cross, Whitman (1854-1949), 1884-1897; cuid311 (Box 7, Folder 310)
  - Cunningham, Robert B., 1899; cuid312 (Box 7, Folder 311)
  - Curtis, George William (1824-1892), 1878; cuid313 (Box 7, Folder 312)
  - Curtis, Josiah (1816-1883), 1875; cuid314 (Box 7, Folder 313)
  - Cusick, C.C., 1874-1882; cuid315 (Box 7, Folder 314)
  - Custer, George Amstrong (1839-1876), 1871; cuid316 (Box 7, Folder 314A)
  - Cutter, E., 1898; cuid317 (Box 7, Folder 315)
  - Dabney, Charles K., 1889; cuid318 (Box 8, Folder 316)
  - Dahlberg, R.H., 1884; cuid319 (Box 8, Folder 317)
  - Dall, William Healey (1845-1927), 1888-1896; cuid320 (Box 8, Folder 318)
  - Dames, Wilhelm Barnirn (1843-1898), 1880-1898; cuid321 (Box 8, Folder 319)
  - Dana, Edward Salisbury (1849-1935), 1895; cuid322 (Box 8, Folder 320)
  - Dana, James Dwight (1813-1895), 1862-1864; cuid323 (Box 8, Folder 321)
  - Dana, James Dwight (1813-1895), 1865-1873; cuid324 (Box 8, Folder 322)
  - Dana, James Dwight (1813-1895), 1879-1892; cuid325 (Box 8, Folder 323)
  - Dana, James Dwight (1813-1895), 1893-1895, undated; cuid326 (Box 8, Folder 324)
  - Darton, Nelson Horatio (1865-1948), 1897-1899; cuid327 (Box 8, Folder 325)
  - Darwin, Charles Carlyle (1848-?), 1890-1897; cuid328 (Box 8, Folder 326)
  - Darwin, Charles Robert (1809-1 882), 1873-1878; cuid329 (Box 8, Folder 327)
  - Darwin, George Howard (1845-1912), 1897; cuid330 (Box 8, Folder 328)
  - Damin, William Erasmus (1839-?), 1878; cuid331 (Box 8, Folder 329)
  - Davidson, George (1825-1911), 1896; cuid332 (Box 8, Folder 330)
  - Davidson, Thomas (1817-1885), 1879-1881; cuid333 (Box 8, Folder 331)
  - Davis, Edward Harvey (1862-1951), 1875-1877; cuid334 (Box 8, Folder 332)
  - Davis, G. Pierrepont, 1898-1899; cuid335 (Box 8, Folder 333)
  - Davis, Henry, 1869; cuid336 (Box 8, Folder 334)
  - Davis, Leander S., 1872-1874; cuid337 (Box 8, Folder 335)
  - Davis, Leander S., 1875-1876; cuid338 (Box 8, Folder 336)
  - Davis, Leander S., 1877-1881; cuid339 (Box 8, Folder 337)
  - Davis, Leander S., 1882-1893; cuid340 (Box 8, Folder 338)
  - Davis, Theodore Russell (1840-1894), 1877-1894; cuid341 (Box 8, Folder 339)
  - Davis, J.M., 1888; cuid342 (Box 8, Folder 340)
  - Davus, William, 1885; cuid343 (Box 8, Folder 341)
  - Dawes, Chester Mitchell (3855-1917), 1898; cuid344 (Box 8, Folder 342)
  - Dawkins, William Boyd (1838-?), 1879-1898; cuid345 (Box 8, Folder 343)
  - Dawson, Sir John William, 1859-1890; cuid346 (Box 8, Folder 344)
  - Day, David Talbot (1859-1925), 1891; cuid347 (Box 8, Folder 345)
  - Day, George Edward (1815-1905), 1889; cuid348 (Box 8, Folder 346)
  - Day, William, 1875-1878; cuid349 (Box 8, Folder 347)
  - DeFree, J. D., 1880; cuid350 (Box 8, Folder 348)
  - DeGolin, L. W., 1880; cuid351 (Box 8, Folder 349)
  - Delavan, D. Bryson, 1894; cuid352 (Box 8, Folder 350)
  - Delp, A.J., 1869-1870; cuid353 (Box 8, Folder 351)
  - DeMasters, F. M., 1890; cuid354 (Box 8, Folder 352)
  - Denfson, Charles H., 1871-1877; cuid355 (Box 8, Folder 353)
  - Dennis, J. M., 1866; cuid356 (Box 8, Folder 354)
  - Detken and Rocholl, 1873; cuid357 (Box 8, Folder 355)
  - Devendorf, Ervin, 1873-1874 May; cuid358 (Box 8, Folder 356)
  - Devendorf, Ervin, 1874 June - November; cuid359 (Box 8, Folder 357)
  - Dewey, Melvil (1851-1931), 1893; cuid360 (Box 8, Folder 358)
  - DeWolf, Austin (1838-?), 1866; cuid361 (Box 8, Folder 359)
  - Dexter, Franklin Bowditch (1842-1920), 1896; cuid362 (Box 8, Folder 360)
  - Dickinson, I.V., 1859; cuid363 (Box 8, Folder 361)
  - Dickinson, M.W., 1875; cuid364 (Box 8, Folder 362)
  - Diller, Joseph Silas (1850-1928), 1888-1895; cuid365 (Box 8, Folder 363)
  - Dimock, Anthony Weston (1842-1918), 1889; cuid366 (Box 9, Folder 364)
  - Dimock, George E., 1889; cuid367 (Box 9, Folder 365)
  - Ditte, Alfred, 1899; cuid368 (Box 9, Folder 365A)
  - Dixon, Edward H, 1882; cuid369 (Box 9, Folder 366)
  - Doane, A. Sidney, 1900; cuid370 (Box 9, Folder 367)
  - Doliheed, R.N., 1884; cuid371 (Box 9, Folder 368)
  - Dooley, A.B, 1869-1876; cuid372 (Box 9, Folder 369)
  - Dotteser, T.D., 1870; cuid373 (Box 9, Folder 370)
  - Dougherty, William J., 1872-1879; cuid374 (Box 9, Folder 371)
  - Douglas, Alexander, 1881; cuid375 (Box 9, Folder 372)
  - Dow, John M., 1872-1874; cuid376 (Box 9, Folder 373)
  - Downing, R.F. and Co., 1891; cuid377 (Box 9, Folder 374)
  - Drake, Charles, undated; cuid378 (Box 9, Folder 375)
  - Draper, Anna Palmer, 1882-1886; cuid379 (Box 9, Folder 376)
  - Draper, Daniel (1841-1931), 1882; cuid380 (Box 9, Folder 377)
  - Draper, John William (1811-1882), 1878; cuid381 (Box 9, Folder 378)
  - Driver, Henry, 1872; cuid382 (Box 9, Folder 379)
  - Denslow, William Wallace (1856-1915), 1866; cuid383 (Box 9, Folder 380)
  - DuBois, C.E., 1872; cuid384 (Box 9, Folder 381)
  - Dumeril, Auguste Henri Andre (1812-1870), 1868-1869; cuid385 (Box 9, Folder 382)
  - Dunning, E.O., 1869-1871; cuid386 (Box 9, Folder 383)
  - Dunning, Joseph, 1887; cuid387 (Box 9, Folder 384)
  - Dupoury, E., 1880; cuid388 (Box 9, Folder 385)
  - Dutton, Clarence Edward (1841-1912), 1866-1869; cuid389 (Box 9, Folder 386)
  - Dwight, Timothy (1752-1817), 1797; cuid390 (Box 9, Folder 387)
  - Dwight, Timothy (1828-1916), 1896-1898; cuid391 (Box 9, Folder 388)
  - Dwight, William Buck (1833-1906), 1887-1893; cuid392 (Box 9, Folder 389)
  - Dyer, C.B., 1867-1870; cuid393 (Box 9, Folder 390)
  - Dyer, John, 1889; cuid394 (Box 9, Folder 391)
  - Earle, Charles, undated; cuid395 (Box 9, Folder 392)
  - Eastman, C.A., 1878; cuid396 (Box 9, Folder 393)
  - Eastman, Charles Rochester (1868-1918), 1894; cuid397 (Box 9, Folder 394)
  - Eaton, Charles G.M., 1866-1867; cuid398 (Box 9, Folder 395)
  - Eaton, Harriet Phelps, undated; cuid399 (Box 9, Folder 396)
  - Eaton, J.R., 1869, 1877; cuid400 (Box 9, Folder 397)
  - Edgar, George W., 1873-1874; cuid401 (Box 9, Folder 398)
  - Edison, Thomas Alva (1847-1933), [1882]; cuid402 (Box 9, Folder 399)
  - Edmunds, George Franklin (1828-1919), 1885; cuid403 (Box 9, Folder 400)
  - Edwards, Arthur M., 1897; cuid404 (Box 9, Folder 401)
  - Edwards, N. M., 1880; cuid405 (Box 9, Folder 402)
  - Egbert, A. A., 1868; cuid406 (Box 9, Folder 403)
  - Ehrman, Henry, 1875; cuid407 (Box 9, Folder 404)
  - Eldodt and Koch, 1876; cuid408 (Box 9, Folder 405)
  - Eldridge, George Homans (1854-1905), 1887-1895; cuid409 (Box 9, Folder 406)
  - Eliot, Charles William (1834-1926), 1878-1888; cuid410 (Box 9, Folder 407)
  - Ely, Edward, 1878; cuid411 (Box 9, Folder 408)
  - Emerson, Benjamin Kendall (1843-1932), 1876; cuid412 (Box 9, Folder 409)
  - Emerson, West and Buckingharn, 1874; cuid413 (Box 9, Folder 410)
  - Emerton, James H. (1847-1930), 1885-1888; cuid414 (Box 9, Folder 411)
  - Emmons, Samuel Franklin (1841-1911), 1876-1891; cuid415 (Box 9, Folder 412)
  - Emmons, Samuel Franklin (1841-1911), 1892-1895; cuid416 (Box 9, Folder 413)
  - Emmons, Samuel Franklin (1841-1911), 1895-1898; cuid417 (Box 9, Folder 414)
  - Encen, H. A., 1867-1868; cuid418 (Box 9, Folder 415)
  - English, J.G., 1876; cuid419 (Box 9, Folder 416)
  - English, James Edward (1812-1890), 1877; cuid420 (Box 9, Folder 417)
  - deErobriand, R., 1873; cuid421 (Box 9, Folder 418)
  - Eustis, Henry Lawrence (1819-1885), 1868; cuid422 (Box 9, Folder 419)
  - Evans, Barton D., 1868; cuid423 (Box 9, Folder 420)
  - Evans, J. M., 1873-1874; cuid424 (Box 9, Folder 421)
  - Evans, John, 1873; cuid425 (Box 9, Folder 422)
  - Evans, S.R., 1871-1877; cuid426 (Box 9, Folder 423)
  - Evans, Walter (1842-1923), 1884; cuid427 (Box 9, Folder 424)
  - Even, J., 1869-1871; cuid428 (Box 9, Folder 425)
  - Everitt, George H., 1878; cuid429 (Box 9, Folder 426)
  - Ewing, Alexander Hamilton (1846-1890), 1870-1871; cuid430 (Box 9, Folder 427)
  - Fackel, Otto, 1899; cuid431 (Box 9, Folder 427A)
  - Fairchild, Charles Stebbins (1842-1924), 1888; cuid432 (Box 9, Folder 428)
  - Farnam, Charles Henry (1846-1909), 1876; cuid433 (Box 9, Folder 429)
  - Farnam, Henry (1803-1883), 1870; cuid434 (Box 9, Folder 430)
  - Farnham, H.E., 1874-1875; cuid435 (Box 9, Folder 431)
  - Farnam, William Whitman (1844-1929), 1892-1898; cuid436 (Box 9, Folder 432)
  - Farnsworth, P.J., 1873; cuid437 (Box 9, Folder 433)
  - Farwell, Charles Benjamin (1823-1903), 1889; cuid438 (Box 9, Folder 434)
  - Faulkner, James Jr., 1874; cuid439 (Box 9, Folder 435)
  - Felch, C.E., 1885; cuid440 (Box 10, Folder 436)
  - Felch, M.P., 1881-1883 June; cuid441 (Box 10, Folder 437)
  - Felch, M.P., 1883 July - September; cuid442 (Box 10, Folder 438)
  - Felch, M.P., 1883 October; cuid443 (Box 10, Folder 439)
  - Felch, M.P., 1883 November; cuid444 (Box 10, Folder 440)
  - Felch, M.P., 1883 December; cuid445 (Box 10, Folder 441)
  - Felch, M.P., 1884 January - February; cuid446 (Box 10, Folder 442)
    For photostats of negatives(reels 5A and 5B) of bone specimens which accompanied Felch correspondence (1884-1885), See also: Common Folio 5, folder 89
  - Felch, M.P., 1884 March - April; cuid447 (Box 10, Folder 443)
  - Felch, M.P., 1884 May - June; cuid448 (Box 10, Folder 444)
  - Felch, M.P., 1884 July - August; cuid449 (Box 10, Folder 445)
  - Felch, M.P., 1884 September - December; cuid450 (Box 10, Folder 446)
  - Felch, M.P., 1885 January - March; cuid451 (Box 10, Folder 447)
  - Felch, M.P., 1885 June - September; cuid452 (Box 10, Folder 448)
  - Felch, M.P., 1885 October - November 16; cuid453 (Box 10, Folder 449)
  - Felch, M.P., 1885 November 17 - December; cuid454 (Box 10, Folder 450)
  - Felch, M.P., 1886 January - March; cuid455 (Box 11, Folder 451)
  - Felch, M.P., 1886 April - June; cuid456 (Box 11, Folder 452)
  - Felch, M.P., 1886 July - September; cuid457 (Box 11, Folder 453)
  - Felch, M.P., 1886 October - December; cuid458 (Box 11, Folder 454)
  - Felch, M.P., 1887 January - June; cuid459 (Box 11, Folder 455)
  - Felch, M.P., 1887 July - December; cuid460 (Box 11, Folder 456)
  - Felch, M.P., 1888 January - June; cuid461 (Box 11, Folder 457)
  - Felch, M.P., 1888 July - December; cuid462 (Box 11, Folder 458)
  - Felch, M.P., 18891-1892; cuid463 (Box 11, Folder 459)
  - Fessender, T.K., 1867; cuid464 (Box 11, Folder 460)
  - Field, Edward, 1869-1871; cuid465 (Box 11, Folder 461)
  - Field, Edward S., 1874-1876; cuid466 (Box 11, Folder 462)
  - Field, D. E., 1869; cuid467 (Box 11, Folder 463)
  - Field, Roswell, 1867-1876; cuid468 (Box 11, Folder 464)
  - Field, S.I., 1874-1876; cuid469 (Box 11, Folder 465)
  - Fields, W.T., 1884-1890; cuid470 (Box 11, Folder 466)
  - Fikenoohen, 1864; cuid471 (Box 11, Folder 467)
  - Fifhold, H., 1887; cuid472 (Box 11, Folder 468)
  - Fischer, Gustav, 1887; cuid473 (Box 11, Folder 469)
  - Fischer, Moritz, 1896-1898; cuid474 (Box 11, Folder 470)
  - Fisher, Miers, 1874; cuid475 (Box 11, Folder 471)
  - Fleugler, J. J., 1857; cuid476 (Box 11, Folder 472)
  - Flower, Georgiana Rosetta, 1885; cuid477 (Box 11, Folder 473)
  - Flower, Sir William Henry (1831-1899), 1873-1898; cuid478 (Box 11, Folder 474)
  - Folwell, W.H., 1870; cuid479 (Box 11, Folder 475)
  - Forbes, William S., 1887; cuid480 (Box 11, Folder 476)
  - Ford, Silas W., 1873-1886; cuid481 (Box 11, Folder 477)
  - Foster, E. K., 1892; cuid482 (Box 11, Folder 478)
  - Foster, Michael (1836-1907), 1895; cuid483 (Box 11, Folder 479)
  - Fraas, Oscar Friedrich von (1824-1897), 1866-1883; cuid484 (Box 11, Folder 480)
  - Fraas, Eberhard (1862-1915), 1895-1896; cuid485 (Box 11, Folder 481)
  - Francis, David Rowland (1850-1927), 1897; cuid486 (Box 11, Folder 482)
  - Francis, James Bicheno (1815-1892), 1884; cuid487 (Box 11, Folder 483)
  - Frantzius, Alexander von (1821-1877), 1872; cuid488 (Box 11, Folder 484)
  - Frey, S.L., 1878; cuid489 (Box 11, Folder 485)
  - Friedberg, M.R., 1873; cuid490 (Box 11, Folder 486)
  - Friedlander, R. and Son, 1881; cuid491 (Box 11, Folder 487)
  - Fritsch, Antonin Jan (1832-1913), 1880-1887; cuid492 (Box 11, Folder 488)
  - Fuller, H. S., 1881; cuid493 (Box 11, Folder 489)
  - Furbinger, M., 1899; cuid494 (Box 11, Folder 489A)
  - Gaines, Marshall Richard (1839-?), 1878; cuid495 (Box 12, Folder 490)
  - G. Amsinck and Co., 1877; cuid496 (Box 12, Folder 490A)
  - Gall, W.M., 1868; cuid497 (Box 12, Folder 491)
  - Galton, Arthur Howard (1852-1921), 1890; cuid498 (Box 12, Folder 492)
  - Galton, Lady Douglas, 1899; cuid499 (Box 12, Folder 492A)
  - Gardner, John Starkie (1844-1930), 1879-1885; cuid500 (Box 12, Folder 493)
  - Garrett, John Work (1820-1884), 1879; cuid501 (Box 12, Folder 494)
  - Gaskill, J.C., 1868-1869; cuid502 (Box 12, Folder 495)
  - Gaudry, Albert (1827-1908), 1881-1898; cuid503 (Box 12, Folder 496)
  - Geare, Randolph Iltyd (1854-1917), 1888-1893; cuid504 (Box 12, Folder 497)
  - Gebhard, W.D., 1886; cuid505 (Box 12, Folder 498)
  - Geilkie, Archibald (1835-1924), 1879-1897; cuid506 (Box 12, Folder 499)
  - Geinitz, Hans Bruno (1814-1900), 1873-1896; cuid507 (Box 12, Folder 500)
  - Geismar, Jacob, 1872; cuid508 (Box 12, Folder 501)
  - Gentile, C., 1878; cuid509 (Box 12, Folder 502)
  - Gernay, Paul, 1876; cuid510 (Box 12, Folder 503)
  - Gerrard, Edward, 1872-1873; cuid511 (Box 12, Folder 504)
  - Gerrard, Edward, 1874-1899; cuid512 (Box 12, Folder 505)
  - Gibbon, John, 1876-1877; cuid513 (Box 12, Folder 506)
  - Gibb, Hugh, 1883-1898; cuid514 (Box 12, Folder 507)
  - Gibbs, Wolcott (1822-1908), 1878-1883; cuid515 (Box 12, Folder 508)
  - Gibbs, Wolcott (1822-1908), 1884-1885; cuid516 (Box 12, Folder 509)
  - Gibbs, Wolcott (1822-1908), 1886-1887; cuid517 (Box 12, Folder 510)
  - Gibbs, Wolcott (1822-1908), 1888-1892; cuid518 (Box 12, Folder 511)
  - Gibbs, Wolcott (1822-1908), 1893-1897; cuid519 (Box 12, Folder 512)
  - Gibson, William L., 1869; cuid520 (Box 12, Folder 513)
  - Gifford, Robert Swain (1840-1905), 1880; cuid521 (Box 12, Folder 514)
  - Giglioli, Enrico H., 1899; cuid522 (Box 12, Folder 514A)
  - Gilbert, Grove Karl (1843-1918), 1868-1883; cuid523 (Box 12, Folder 515)
  - Gilbert, Grove Karl (1843-1918), 1885-1889; cuid524 (Box 12, Folder 516)
  - Gilder, Richard Watson (1844-1909), 1897; cuid525 (Box 12, Folder 517)
  - Gilder, William Henry (1838-1900), 1890; cuid526 (Box 12, Folder 518)
  - Gill, Theodore Nicholas (1837-1914), 1867-1874; cuid527 (Box 12, Folder 519)
  - Gillurn, George, 1869; cuid528 (Box 12, Folder 520)
  - Gilman, Daniel Colt (1831-1908), 1857-1886; cuid529 (Box 12, Folder 521)
  - Gilmore, C.M., 1888; cuid530 (Box 12, Folder 522)
  - Glahn, George A., 1894; cuid531 (Box 12, Folder 523)
  - Glass, J.W., 1871; cuid532 (Box 12, Folder 524)
  - Gleason, W.T., 1867-1870; cuid533 (Box 12, Folder 525)
  - Goldbacher, Joseph, 1872-1873; cuid534 (Box 12, Folder 526)
  - Goodale, George Lincoln (1839-1923), 1892-1895; cuid535 (Box 12, Folder 527)
  - Goode, George Brown (1851-1896), 1877-1888; cuid536 (Box 12, Folder 528)
  - Goode, George Brown (1851-1896), 1889-1890; cuid537 (Box 12, Folder 529)
  - Goode, George Brown (1851-1896), 1891-1893; cuid538 (Box 12, Folder 530)
  - Goode, George Brown (1851-1896), 1894-1896; cuid539 (Box 12, Folder 531)
  - Goodrich, Caspar Frederick (1847-1925), 1875; cuid540 (Box 13, Folder 532)
  - Goodwin, Francis, 1892; cuid541 (Box 13, Folder 533)
  - Gore, James Howard (1856-?), 1883; cuid542 (Box 13, Folder 534)
  - Gore, N.B., 1874; cuid543 (Box 13, Folder 535)
  - Gottschalck, August, 1884; cuid544 (Box 13, Folder 536)
  - Gould, Benjamin Apthorp (1824-1896), 1870-1895; cuid545 (Box 13, Folder 537)
  - Grant, Ulyses Simpson (1822-1885), 1875; cuid546 (Box 13, Folder 538)
  - Gray, Asa (1810-1888), 1866-1885; cuid547 (Box 13, Folder 539)
  - Greely, Adolphus Washington (1844-1935), 1884-1888; cuid548 (Box 13, Folder 540)
  - Green, Alexander Henry (1832-1896), 1890-1891; cuid549 (Box 13, Folder 541)
  - Green, C.J., 1890; cuid550 (Box 13, Folder 542)
  - Green, James, 1870; cuid551 (Box 13, Folder 543)
  - Greg, Robert Phillips (1826-1906), 1855; cuid552 (Box 13, Folder 544)
  - Gregory, S.S., 1873; cuid553 (Box 13, Folder 545)
  - Gresham, Walter Quintin (1832-1895), 1893; cuid554 (Box 13, Folder 546)
  - Grinnell, George Bird (1849-1938), 1871-1872; cuid555 (Box 13, Folder 547)
  - Grinnell, George Bird (1849-1938), 1873-1885; cuid556 (Box 13, Folder 548)
  - Groat, P.B., 1879; cuid557 (Box 13, Folder 549)
  - Grube, Edward (1812-1880), 1865-1873; cuid558 (Box 13, Folder 550)
  - Gruber, F., 1872-1878; cuid559 (Box 13, Folder 551)
  - Gruen, James A. and Co., 1876; cuid560 (Box 13, Folder 552)
  - Guernsey, C.A., 1889; cuid561 (Box 13, Folder 553)
  - Guild, Edward W., 1876-1878 June; cuid562 (Box 13, Folder 554)
  - Guild, Edward W., 1878 July - 1880; cuid563 (Box 13, Folder 555)
  - Guin, F.M., 1889; cuid564 (Box 13, Folder 556)
  - Gundlack, George, 1875; cuid565 (Box 13, Folder 557)
  - Curley, William, 1876; cuid566 (Box 13, Folder 558)
  - Guyot, Arnold Henry (1807-1884), 1869-1883; cuid567 (Box 13, Folder 559)
  - Haast, Julius von (1822-1887), 1872-1878; cuid568 (Box 13, Folder 560)
  - Haeckel, Ernest (1834-1919), 1885-1895; cuid569 (Box 13, Folder 561)
  - Hague, Arnold (1840-1917), 1871-1886; cuid570 (Box 13, Folder 562)
  - Hague, Arnold (1840-1917), 1892-1895; cuid571 (Box 13, Folder 563)
  - Hague, James D. (1836-1908), 1877; cuid572 (Box 13, Folder 564)
  - Haines, George (1798-1877), 1868-1870; cuid573 (Box 13, Folder 565)
  - Hale, Edward Everett (1822-1909), 1879-1893; cuid574 (Box 13, Folder 566)
  - Hall, Asaph (1829-1907), 1880-1883; cuid575 (Box 14, Folder 567)
  - Hall, Asaph (1829-1907), 1884 January - June; cuid576 (Box 14, Folder 568)
  - Hall, Asaph (1829-1907), 1885; cuid577 (Box 14, Folder 569)
  - Hall, Asaph (1829-1907), 1886; cuid578 (Box 14, Folder 570)
  - Hall, Asaph (1829-1907), 1887; cuid579 (Box 14, Folder 571)
  - Hall, Asaph (1829-1907), 1888; cuid580 (Box 14, Folder 572)
  - Hall, Asaph (1829-1907), 1889-1890; cuid581 (Box 14, Folder 573)
  - Hall, Asaph (1829-1907), 1891; cuid582 (Box 14, Folder 574)
  - Hall, Asaph (1829-1907), 1892-1893; cuid583 (Box 14, Folder 575)
  - Hall, Asaph (1829-1907), 1894-1898; cuid584 (Box 14, Folder 576)
  - Hall, Asaph (1829-1907), 1893; cuid585 (Box 14, Folder 577)
  - Hall, Asaph, Jr. (1859-1930), 1893; cuid586 (Box 14, Folder 578)
  - Hall, Christopher Webber (1845-1911), 1884; cuid587 (Box 14, Folder 579)
  - Hall, J., 1885; cuid588 (Box 14, Folder 580)
  - Hall, James (1811-1898), 1867-1893; cuid589 (Box 14, Folder 581)
  - Halvorsen, M.C., 1891; cuid590 (Box 14, Folder 582)
  - Hamback, Dr. S., 1879; cuid591 (Box 14, Folder 583)
  - Hamilton, James M., 1896-1897; cuid592 (Box 14, Folder 584)
  - Hamlin, Augustus Choate (1829-1905), 1870-1874; cuid593 (Box 14, Folder 585)
  - Hammond Typewriter Company, 1898; cuid594 (Box 14, Folder 586)
  - Hampson, Thomas, 1886-1887; cuid595 (Box 14, Folder 587)
  - Hand and Post, 1874; cuid596 (Box 14, Folder 588)
  - Hanks, Henry G. (1826-1907), 1872-1879; cuid597 (Box 14, Folder 589)
  - Hare, Sid J., 1884; cuid598 (Box 14, Folder 590)
  - Harger, Oscar (1843-1887), 1872-1887; cuid599 (Box 14, Folder 591)
  - Harper, George W., 1870-1872; cuid600 (Box 14, Folder 592)
  - Harper, William Rainey (1856-1906), 1893; cuid601 (Box 14, Folder 593)